<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>Hi, my name is Andrew.</title>
		<description></description>
		<link>https://himynameisandrew.com</link>
		<atom:link href="https://himynameisandrew.com/rss/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
					<item>
				<title>In Defense of Classes</title>
				<description>A few months ago, Tim Baxter wrote a post for A List Apart titled _Meaningful CSS: Style Like You Mean It_. In it, he lays out an argument for avoiding the use of classes in markup and instead favoring things like attributes which make your markup more meaningful and elements as CSS selectors. There are parts of his idea that I like, but overall I don’t think it’s all that practical for many projects other than very small websites or apps.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 12:00:00 EST</pubDate>
				<link>http://himynameisandrew.com/blog/in-defense-of-classes/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://himynameisandrew.com/blog/in-defense-of-classes/</guid>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Practical Uses for Flexbox</title>
				<description>If you’ve been developing for the web in the past couple of years, you have most likely heard of CSS’s Flexible box layout module (also known as flexbox). Maybe you’ve used it, or maybe you’ve shied away from it in favor of more familiar layout methods. I’ve been using flexbox fairly regularly for the past few months and I have to say, it’s pretty amazing. Here are some practical uses that I have found.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2016 12:00:00 EST</pubDate>
				<link>http://himynameisandrew.com/blog/practical-uses-for-flexbox/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://himynameisandrew.com/blog/practical-uses-for-flexbox/</guid>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Using CSS Masks to Create “Transparent” JPGs</title>
				<description>JPG images are great. They allow us to show photos on the web while keeping the file size relatively small (compared to a photo saved as a PNG, anyway). But what do you do when you need a photo with transparency and you don’t want to sacrifice file size? Enter CSS masks.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 12:00:00 EST</pubDate>
				<link>http://himynameisandrew.com/blog/using-css-masks-to-create-transparent-jpgs/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://himynameisandrew.com/blog/using-css-masks-to-create-transparent-jpgs/</guid>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Apple CarPlay: First Impressions</title>
				<description>A little over a week ago, I got a new car which came equipped with Apple CarPlay. If you’re not familiar with CarPlay, it’s essentially a platform that allows you to replace your car’s built-in user interface with an interface that runs off your iPhone. I’ve spent some time with it and wanted to share some of my initial thoughts.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 12:00:00 EST</pubDate>
				<link>http://himynameisandrew.com/blog/apple-carplay-first-impressions/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://himynameisandrew.com/blog/apple-carplay-first-impressions/</guid>
			</item>
			</channel>
</rss>
